steply.com 2013-11-27

# Steply

## Privacy Policy

Stepcase Limited ("Stepcase," "we," or "us") knows that you care about how information about you is used and shared. This Privacy Policy covers Stepcase’s treatment of personally identifiable information (“Personal Information”) that Stepcase collects when you are accessing our Service. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Stepcase does not own or control, or to individuals that Stepcase does not employ or manage. In addition, the Service contains links to outside sources, both ones we have added ourselves and ones that members have submitted. While we attempt to provide links only to those sites that share our respect for your privacy, we cannot take responsibility for the content or privacy policies of those sites. We strongly encourage you to carefully review the privacy policies of any web sites you visit.

When visiting or using any of Stepcase's website, services, applications, or content offered from time to time by Stepcase in connection therewith (collectively, the "Service"), you consent to the collection, transfer, manipulation, storage, disclosure and other uses of your information as described in this Privacy Policy.

### What Information Do We Collect?

User-Provided Information: When you create or update a Stepcase account, you provide some Personal Information, such as your name, username, password, and email address. When using the Service, you may also provide certain other Personal Information and content, such as photos, locations and activities, which will be publicly displayed to other Users and on third-party sites and services.

  1. Location Information: You may choose to add your location on your photos. You can control your location information settings before uploading your photo. To provide this feature, we derive location information from your wireless carrier, certain third-party service providers, or directly from the mobile device that you use a Stepcase mobile application. This location tracking of your mobile device occurs only when a Stepcase mobile application is actively open and running.
  2. Cookies Information: Like many websites, we use "cookie" technology to collect additional website usage data and to improve our Services, but we do not require cookies for many parts of our Services such as searching and looking at public user profiles or lists. A cookie is a small data file that is transferred to your computer's hard disk. We may use both session cookies and persistent cookies to better understand how you interact with our Services, to monitor aggregate usage by our users and web traffic routing on our Services, and to improve our Services. You can reset your web browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some features of the Service may not function properly if the ability to accept cookies is disabled.
  3. Log Data: Our servers automatically record information ("Log Data") created by your use of the Services. Log Data may include information such as your IP address, browser type, the referring domain, pages visited, and search terms. Other actions, such as interactions with advertisements, may also be included in Log Data.
  4. Third Party Services: Stepcase uses Google Analytics & Flurry Analytics to help understand use of our services. Through Google, Analytics collects the information sent by your browser as part of a web page request, including cookies and your IP address. Google also receives this information and their use of it is governed by their Privacy Policy. Through Flurry, Analytics collects information sent by your mobile device as part of the data requests when you interact with Steply. We encrypt username data to ensure accounts are not identifiable. Flurry also receives this information and their use of it is governed by their Privacy Policy.

### How Do We Use Your Information?

  1. Provide Best Functions: We use the Personal Information we collect to operate, maintain, and provide to you the best features and functionality of the Service. Publication with Your consent: Any Personal Information, pictures or content that you voluntarily disclose for posting to the Service (including your geo-tagged messages and user content) becomes available to the public instantly. Stepcase is not responsible for the personally identifiable, profile, or location information that you choose to disclose publicly on the Service. If you remove information that you posted to the Service, copies may remain viewable in cached or archived pages of the Service, or if other Users have copied or saved that information.
  2. Email Communication: We may receive a confirmation when you open an account from Stepcase. We use this confirmation to help us make emails more interesting and helpful to serve you better in the future. If you do not want to receive email or other offers from us, please indicate your preference during the registration process or by making a modification on your account settings page.

### Do We Disclose Your Information?

Your personal information is an integral part of our business. We neither rent nor sell your personal information to anyone. Your private information may be shared only in the limited circumstances described here.

  1. Promotional Offers: As part of the Service you may be exposed to offers on behalf of other businesses. In certain situations, these businesses provide free gifts or sell items to you through Stepcase’s Service. However, we will only share your personal information that is necessarily related to such transactions with that affiliated business.
  2. User Profiles and Invitations: User profile information including user name, Twitter and Facebook account name, and other information you enter may be displayed to other users to facilitate user interaction within the Service. Users’ real names will not be revealed by us, except, when you invite someone to join the Stepcase community. This information is necessary to make sure your invitee knows who has contacted them so as to build a community based on trust and empathy.
  3. Third party links: Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.
  4. With Your Consent: We may share or disclose your information only with your consent.
  5. Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement: Stepcase may disclose your information if we believe that it is reasonably necessary to comply with a law, regulation or legal request; to protect the safety of any person; to address fraud, security or technical issues; to investigate and defend ourselves against any third-party claims or allegations; or to protect our rights or property.
  6. Business Transfers: In the event that Stepcase is involved in a bankruptcy, merger, acquisition, reorganization or sale of assets, customer information is typically one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of Stepcase may continue to use your Personal Information as set forth in this policy.
  7. Non-Private or Non-Personal Information: We may share or disclose your non-private, aggregated or otherwise non-personal information, such as your public comments or the number of users who clicked on a particular link (even if only one did).

### What Choices Do I have?

  1. Email Communication: Stepcase may contact you through your registered email address when there is a new follower, comment, or “like” to you or your photo. If you do not wish to receive these emails from us, please indicate your preference on your account settings page.
  2. Social Network Connections: As Stepcase wants to make things easier for you, once you choose to link your Stepcase account with your Facebook or Twitter, any publications on Stepcase will be automatically updated to your linked social network accounts. If you do not want such updates to be taken place, you can unlink your social network accounts under your account settings page.
  3. Publication: It is important to note that any kinds of publication, including your geo-tagged photos, from you are disclosed to the public automatically with your consent. If you desire privacy for any piece of content, it is strongly advised that you should not upload it to Stepcase.

### Is Personal Information About Me Secure?

Your Stepcase account Personal Information is protected by a password for your privacy and security. You need to prevent unauthorized access to your account and Personal Information by selecting and protecting your password appropriately and limiting access to your computer and browser by signing off after you have finished accessing your account. Although we cannot guarantee the security of user account information, Stepcase endeavors to protect user information to ensure that user account information is kept private.

Since the Service may contain links to other sites, Stepcase is not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices on those sites. When linking to another site, you should read the privacy policy stated there in order to protect yourself better. This Privacy Policy only governs information collected on the Service.

### Children's Privacy

Stepcase does not knowingly collect or solicit Personal Information from anyone under the age of 13 or knowingly allow such persons to register as Members. If you become aware that your child has provided us with Personal Information without your consent, please contact us at privacy [at] stepcase.com. If we become aware that a child under 13 has provided us with Personal Information, we take steps to remove such information and terminate the child's account.

### Terms and Conditions

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at <http://steply.com/terms>

### Changes to Our Privacy Policy

We may revise this Privacy Policy from time to time so as to protect you better. Users are bound by any changes to the Privacy Policy when he or she uses the Service after such changes have been first posted. The most current version of the policy will be on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below.

This policy was last modified on June 21, 2010

### Contacting Us

If you have any questions or concerns regarding this privacy policy, please contact us at privacy [at] stepcase.com.
